Hello, I am Mr. Stock. Secondly, today
we will learn about the stocks on which the
world's top brokerage firms have
started their coverage. The brokerage firm has given a
rating along with a target price on this stock. Let's
know in detail in the stock of i40 Talk.
Friends, the first stock is ICC
Lombard.
Motilal Oswal, the top brokerage firm in the domestic market, has
provided a rating on the stock of ICC Lombard, an insurance sector company. The brokerage
firm has set a target price of Rs 1550 for the stock.
Motilal Oswal believes that
ICC Lombard is showing great potential to move forward on the path of growth
with the changes taking place in the insurance industry of India.
Let's now talk about the second stock, Mankind Pharma.
Friends, Jaffery, the
world's most famous brokerage
firm, has given a hold rating on Mankind Pharma. For example, he has
given a target of Rs 1000830 on the health care sector stock.
Mankind Pharma Company is a strong
franchise. Many aspects are being seen in this month
which will help in the
better performance of the company in the coming near future.  We
can help. Let's talk about the third stock delivery.
Friends, Birthday has
provided an out of perform rating on the new-age stock delivery and has
given its target of ₹460. Friends,
brokerage firms are expecting a rise from this company due to the improvement in the company's cash flow as well as the fixes
and improvements made by the company at low cost.
Let's now
talk about the last stock, Suzlon.
Among the top brokerage firms of the domestic market, ICC has
given a buy rating on Suzlon stock on Monday and has
given a target of ₹22 on the stock. The brokerage firms
believe that Suzlon company is
far ahead in the market compared to its competitors in terms of margin.
Friends, experts also believe
that the renewable industry is improving very rapidly
and this can benefit
Suzlon company.
Which of these four stocks do you have
in your stock portfolio? Friends, if you want to know
when to buy shares of which company or
when to sell shares of which company
So you can follow our Telegram channel, so
friends, that's all for now in this video, see you
in the next video.